(Leonard:)Yes.
(Sheldon:)Then I suppose
you could have agreed to go.
(Leonard:)And what would I have said afterwards?
(Sheldon:)I would suggest something
to the effect of:
"Singing is neither an appropriate vocation
nor avocation for you...
...and if you disagree, I recommend
a CAT scan to look for a tumor...
(Sheldon:)...pressing on the cognitive
processing centers of your brain."
(Leonard:)I couldn't say that.
I would have to say, "You were terrific
and I can't wait to hear you sing again."
(Penny:)Why?
(Leonard:)It's the social protocol.
(Leonard:)It's what you do...
(Leonard:)...when you have a friend who's proud
of something they really suck at.
(Sheldon:)I was not aware of that.
- Well, now you are.
- Oh, all right.
- Leonard?
- Yes?
(Sheldon:)When we played chess earlier, you were
terrific, and I can't wait to play you again.
Good night.
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
SHELDON:
Leonard? Leonard?
(Leonard:)This would be so much easier
if I were a violent sociopath.